In my own oppinion the most popular programming languages are Java,Javascript,PHP,C,C#.
1)Java-programs written in Java, can run on many different computer architectures and operating systems
 thanks to the use of the JVM (Java Virtual Machine).Java language is well organized with rich functionality in
 the standard libraries that can be used many times.
2)Javascript is the most popular programming language on the Internet. JavaScript is a language for writing scripts.
JavaScript is easier to encode compared to languages ​​like Java and C ++. 
The trend in the future is to build more and more complex applications in JavaScript.
3)PHP is a scripting programming language used for server applications and developing dynamic web content.
PHP is web programming language.
4)C is one of the most widely imposed programming languages ​​of all time. Although the C language is relatively old,
 it is still widely used for system programming, writing to other programming languages ​​as well as in embedded systems.
5)C # is simple, modern, object-oriented language, with full purpose written by Microsoft. 
C # is considered a high quality programming language using the .NET platform.One of the biggest advantages of 
the .NET Framework has built-in automatic memory management. It prevents programmers from the complex task 
themselves to allocate memory for objects and look for the right time for its release. 
This seriously increases the productivity of developers and increases the quality of programs written in C #.


