An integrated development environment (IDE) is a software application that provides comprehensive facilities 
to computer programmers for software development. An IDE normally consists of a source code editor,
 build automation tools and a debugger.
Here are five  popular IDEs:
1)Microsoft visual studio-its products cover languages like C++, C# and VB.NET.
 In addition, you are also able to develop for the Windows x86, Windows RT, and Windows Phone. 
2)Oracle netbeans-this is IDE for Java,but supports C,C++, Ruby, HTML5, PHP and more.
 Netbeans is extremely extensible via its plugin-centric design, allowing to 
add additional language syntax support and libraries, among other things.
3)Eclipse-this IDE is quite comprehensive and even similar to Netbeans in a variety of ways, including its use of Java and plugin architecture. 